我们并没有在我们的天气表中存储任何
We're not storing a key piece of data in our weather table,
当地天气将要呈现的情况
the location at which the weather is going to occur.
这是因为我们将要为天气位置使用一个分离的表
This is because we are going to use a separate table for weather locations.
使用一个分离的表有很多优势
Using a separate table has several advantages.
因为我们没有给每一条记录增加一条位置信息所以会很高效
In addition to being more efficient because we do not duplicate our location
并且这使得我们在更新位置信息的时候
data with each record, it also allows us to update information about our
不需要更新所有的天气预报记录
location without having to update every weather forecast record.
为了达成这一目标  我们要创建我们的天气和位置数据库之间的关联
To implement this, we're going to create a relation between our weather and
而这个关联是通过在天气表中添加一个关联到
location tables by adding a column to the weather table that refers to an ID
位置表的ID的列
in the location table.
这个列通过一个约束条件来创建并指定它是一个
This column is created with a constraint that identifies it as a foreign key,
与其他的表相独立的ID的外键
which is a unique ID from another table.
这像什么呢
What does this look like?
我们的天气表中的列有一个位置ID
Our list of columns in the weather table has a location ID,
这个ID指向位置表的相应ID
which points to IDs in the location table.
我们可以使用这个位置ID来进行内连接操作
We can use this location ID to perform an operation known as an inner join.
内连接把在不同表中查询的两个行数据结合到
Inner joins combine the data queried from two rows in different tables into
结果的一行
one row in the results.
当我们通过这种方式创建我们的表我可以得到
When we create our tables in this way we can get any combination of
两个表的任意结合的列
columns from both tables.
在这个例子中我们可以在位置表中进行位置查询
In this case we're getting the location query from the location table, and
以及从天气表中得到数据  描述  最低和最高温度
the date, description, and min and max temperature from the weather table